In 1917, in the midst of a world war, people
needed hope. They received a miracle.
Fatima is a drama film directed by Marco Pontecorvo.
In 1917, outside the parish of Fátima, Portugal, a 10-year-old girl and her two younger cousins witness multiple
visitations of the Virgin Mary, who tells them that only prayer and suffering will bring an end to World War I.
As secularist government officials and Church leaders try to force the children to recant their story, word of the sighting
spreads across the country, inspiring religious pilgrims to flock to the site in hopes of witnessing a miracle..
Professor Nichols, played by Harvey Keitel.
Sister Lucia, played by Sônia Braga.
Artur, played by Goran Višnjić.
Father Ferreira, played by Joaquim de Almeida.
Maria Rosa, played by Lúcia Moniz.
Mary, played by Joana Ribeiro.
Fátima is a 2020 faith-based drama film directed by Marco Pontecorvo.
It stars Joaquim de Almeida, Goran Višnjić, Harvey Keitel, Sônia Braga,
Stephanie Gil, Alejandra Howard, Jorge Lamelas and Lúcia Moniz.
The film, based on Our Lady of Fátima, features the original song "Gratia Plena" ("Full of
Grace"), performed by Andrea Bocelli and composed by Italian composer Paolo Buonvino.
The tone is uplifting and emotional.